얘들아
I got my teacher evaluations.
Look what this student wrote.
강의평가서를 받았는데
한 학생이 쓴 걸 좀 봐
"I loved Dr. Geller's class.
Mind-blowing lectures.
'겔러 박사님 강의 너무 좋아요
정말 감동적이에요'
'박사님은 명실상부한
고생물학과의 킹카예요'
You are definitely the hottie
of the Paleontology Department."
고생물학과의 킹카라
누군 잘나가는구만, 어?
"Hotties of Paleontology."
There's a big-selling calendar.
-Who wrote it?
-The evaluations are all anonymous.
누가 썼는데?
나도 알고 싶지만
평가서는 익명이야
- 마지막 시험지 갖고 있어?
- 그럼
-You have their exams?
-Yeah.
필적을 비교해보면 되잖아
짠, 바로 걸리는 거지
You could just match the handwriting
and there's your admirer.
A hot girl's at stake
and he's Rain Man.
여자 하나 말뚝에 매달고
불을 질러라
근데 잠깐만
Wait a minute. Why are we
so sure that this is a girl?
이게 왜 여자라고 생각하지?
여자가 아니면
It's a girl!
But it wouldn't matter.
어쨌든 별일이야 생기겠어?
선생과 제자 사이인데
Because I'm a teacher.
She's a student.
교칙에 어긋나?
-It's illegal?
-It's frowned upon.
- 아니, 지탄의 대상이지
- 알았다
-And there's a big age gap.
-When you're 90..
게다가 나이차도 커
이렇게 생각해봐
네가 아흔일 때...
I know, she'll be 80 and it won't
seem like such a big difference.
내가 아흔이면 걔는 여든
별 차이 아니라는 거지?
That's not what I was gonna say.
아니, 그런 말이 아닌데
아흔이 되더라도 20살짜리를
사귀던 추억이 남을 거라고
When you're 90, you'll still have the
memory of being with a 20-year-old.
The One Where Ross Dates A Student
-Monica..?
-I don't know.
모니카?
- 난 몰라
- 그래
야, 챈들러
You know your college friend
who became a movie director?
네 동창 중에
영화감독 된 사람 알지?
Oh yeah, Dana Keystone.
She was in my movement class.
그래, 데이나 키스톤
같이 동작 수업 들었어
동작 수업이 뭐야?
-What's a movement class?
-He's pretending he didn't take mime.
마임 수업 받은 거
숨기고 싶으면 하는 소리야
She's directing a new Al Pacino movie.
You gotta get me an audition.
어쨌든 그 여자가 알 파치노의
새 영화를 감독한대
나 오디션 좀 받게 해주라
글쎄다, 안 본 지
10년도 넘었거든
I haven't talked to her in 10 years.
부탁 좀 하자
신세는 꼭 갚을게
Please, Chandler,
I would owe you so much.
지금도 갚을 거 엄청 많아
You do owe me so much.
You owe me 3000..
- 보자, 3천 4백...
- 임마
Hey, hey, dude. Why you changing
the subject? What?
왜 화제를 바꿔
전화 안 해줄래?
-Will you make the call?
-Okay, I'll try.
알았어, 해볼게
그래, 역시 너밖에 없다
마지막 오디션이 목요일이야
Thanks. Last auditions are Thursday,
so I gotta get in by Thursday.
늦어도 목요일까진 가야 해
목요일을 기억해, 목요일
목요일 기억할 수 있겠냐?
Remember Thursday.
Remember Thursday?
그래, 화요일이라고?
Yeah, so Tuesday?
Thursday!
목요일
외우는 방법을 가르쳐줄게
Just think of it like this:
The third day. Monday, one day.
세 번째 날이야, 됐지?
월요일은 첫 번째 날
화요일은 두 번째 날
Tuesday, two day.
수요일은? 응, 뭐라고?
목요일이구나!
Wednesday...
When day, what day?
Thursday!
The third day, okay?
세 번째 다음날, 알았어?
-Thank you.
-Okay.
- 고맙다
- 그래
-Hey, Monica..?
-She doesn't know.
- 야, 모니카
- 쟤도 모른대
-I'm gonna check my messages.
-You thought of that in there?
모니카, 메시지 확인 좀 할게
일보면서 그 생각했냐?
Nature called.
She wants to see who else did.
자연의 부름을 받으니
다른 부름도 궁금했겠지
Hello?
여보세요?
레이첼인데요?
Rachel.
Someone's in our apartment.
Call the cops!
우리 아파트에 누가 있어
경찰에 신고해
You're on the phone!
전화기 너한테 있잖아
-Oh, my God!
-What?
- 맙소사
- 왜?
세상에, 고맙습니다
Oh, my God! Thank you!
There was a fire at our place.
우리 아파트에 불났대
맙소사, 심각한 거야?
-Oh, my God! How bad was it?
-It was a fire, I'm guessing not good.
그런 얘기는 안 했지만
불이 났으니 좋기야 하겠니?
- 빨리 가보자
- 서둘러
-Come on, we gotta go!
-Yeah, come on.
What are you smiling about?
넌 뭐가 좋아서 웃고 있냐?
The part I want to audition for is
a fireman. This is so meant to be!
오디션 볼 역이 소방관이야
이건 하늘의 계시라고
You were very generous
with your grades this semester.
저런
이번 학기에 점수가
너무 후하시네요
-Professor Geller?
-Yeah?
- 겔러 교수님?
- 네?
교수님 강의 정말 좋았어요
-I really enjoyed your class.
-Oh, thank you. Thanks very much.
오, 고마워요
다행이군요, 아야!
평가서에 킹카라고 해서
놀라진 않으셨나요?
I'm a little embarrassed about
calling you a hottie.
-That was you?
-Yeah.
- 그게 학생이었어요?
- 네
기분이 좀 이상하네요
한쪽은 스승, 한쪽은 제자
I felt a little weird about it.
You're a teacher. I'm a student.
언제 저 한 번 만나주실래요?
Want to go out sometime?
That's not the best idea.
그건 별로 좋은 생각이
아닌 것 같군요
Oh, because I was thinking,
the semester's over.
생각해 봤는데...
이번 학기가 끝났으니까
-You're not my teacher anymore.
-What time?
더 이상 사제지간이 아니에요
언제가 좋을까?
Oh, you know what? Forget it.
아뇨, 그만두죠
벌써 A를 주셨네요
I see you already gave me an A.
-Gotcha.
-I'm kidding! God!
알았어요
농담이에요
So seriously, what time?
그럼 진지하게
언제가 좋을까?
Coming through. Coming through.
Oh! Hello. Hi.
비켜주세요, 실례해요
안녕하세요
반가워요
Right. Coming through!
안 되지, 비켜주세요
Okay. It's not so bad.
그렇게 많이 타진 않았네
Most of the damage
was contained to the bedrooms.
불길은 침실 쪽으로
집중됐습니다
맙소사
Hey, buddy, think I could borrow
your uniform this Thursday?
저기, 목요일에 유니폼
좀 빌릴 수 있을까요?
-Excuse me?
-Joey! He's working.
뭐라고요?
조이, 근무 중이시잖아
You would look good in that.
자기가 입으면 참 멋지겠다
Oh, how bad is it?
많이 탔니?
너무 심각하다, 남은 건
도끼 한 자루밖에 없는데
It's really bad.
The only thing that isn't burned is an
ax, which I do not remember buying.
내가 그걸 왜 샀지?
-How's your room?
-Everything's ruined.
네 방은 어때, 레이첼?
전부 잿더미야
침대며 옷이며
My bed, my clothes.
Look at my favorite sweater.
내가 제일 아끼던
파란색 스웨터야
Isn't that mine?
내 거 아냐?
Fine. I'm sorry for your loss.
그래, 진심으로 애도를 표한다
You won't be able to live here for
a while. You have a place to stay?
여기선 지내기 힘드실 텐데
어디 계실 만한 곳은 있나요?
Oh! Wow!
Okay, look, pal...
좋아요
이거 보세요
I am not in the mood
to be hit on right now.
나 지금은 도저히
그럴 기분이 아니지만
But if you give me your number,
I'll call you sometime.
전화번호를 주시면
나중에 연락 드리죠
Yes, they can stay with us.
네, 저희 집에서 지내면 돼요
Do you know what
started the fire, Mr. Fireman?
화재원인이 밝혀졌나요
소방관 아저씨?
Well, do either of you smoke?
혹시 담배 피우시나요?
No. But yeah,
I could use one now. Thanks.
평소엔 아니지만
지금은 한 대 주세요
아뇨, 그렇다면 초나
향 같은 걸 태우십니까?
-Do you light candles, burn incense?
-I do all the time. I love them!
네, 제가 좋아해서
늘 태우는데...
Oh, my God, I did it! It's me,
it's me! I burned down the house!
맙소사, 내가 그랬구나
내가 집을 태워먹었어
Okay, Phoebe, calm down.
There's no need to place blame. Okay?
피비, 진정해
누구 탓할 때가 아냐
I warned her about those candles.
전 늘 주의를 줬거든요
세상에, 너무 반갑다
이게 얼마만이야?
I can't believe how long it's been.
챈들러, 혹시...
Hey, Chandler, is that..?
-Oh, that's great, good for you.
-So, is it..?
그래, 정말 잘됐다
야...
Okay. So, yeah, maybe
we can get together...
언제 한 번 만나지 뭐...
Hold on for one second.
잠깐만 기다려줄래?
What?
뭐야?
Do you want to get a pizza later?
통화 끝나고 피자 먹을래?
Hi, I'm back.
그래, 얘기해
Yeah, that sounds great.
We'll do it then. Okay, bye.
그거 좋지
그때 보자고
이만 끊을게
내 오디션은 언제지?
정확히 목요일 몇 시냐고
When's my audition?
I know it's Thursday, but what time?
Hi. We didn't get to it.
- 어서 와
- 그래
아직 그 얘긴 안 꺼냈어
커피 한 잔 하면서 말할게
I'm taking her to coffee.
We'll do it then.
그 여자랑 데이트를 하시겠다?
Now you're going on a date
with this girl?
데이트라니
I haven't talked to her in 10 years.
10년 만에 대뜸 전화를 걸어
부탁하는 건 경우가 아니잖아
You can't just call up
and ask somebody for a favor.
There are rules, you know?
You gotta put in some time.
차근차근 풀어야지
Right, I'm sorry.
그래, 미안해
-It's not like she's an ex-girlfriend.
-We only went out once.
옛날 애인도 아닌데 뭐
한 번 만나긴 했어
You dated her?!
데이트까지 했다고?
Not once.
한 번도 안 만났어
Why don't I just go out with an ex,
you know, and do Joey a favor?
좋아, 나도 옛날 애인 만나서
조이 좀 부탁해야겠다
You want to do Joey a favor?
Maybe you go out with Joey.
조이를 생각해준다면
조이랑 사귀면 돼
That's great. My friend Joey's
in the movie business.
잘됐다, 내 친구 조이도
영화 쪽 일을 하는데
You know who I ran into from school?
Howie.
저번에 우리 동창
하위를 우연히 만났어
My friend's name is Joey.
내 친구 이름은 조이야
Apparently, Howie's editing now.
하위는 영화편집을 하더라고
Yeah, he calls me up and asks me
if he can edit my new movie.
갑자기 전화해선 내 영화를
편집해도 되냐고 묻는 거야
Can you believe that?
기막히지 않니?
10년 동안 연락 끊고 살다가
툭 튀어나와서 부탁을 해?
You know, I haven't spoken to him
in 10 years...
and he asks me for a favor?
Yeah, I've always hated that Howie.
나도 하위 싫어했어
No "How you doing?"
잘 지냈냐는 얘기도 없어
Man, I mean, not even
a cup of coffee first.
커피 한 잔이라도
샀으면 말을 안 해
- 뻔뻔하다, 그렇지?
- 누가 아니래
-The nerve.
-Yeah.
Refill?
커피 더 마셔라
시간이 없어서 대충
치웠으니까 이해해
This is last-minute, so I want
to apologize for the mess.
- 그래
- 괜찮아
Oh, who cares?
Oh, my God! It sure didn't look
this way when I lived here.
세상에
완전 딴판으로 변했다
그렇지?
I know!
안됐지만 이 침대는 싱글이라
한 사람은 조이 집으로 가야겠다
But there's only room for one, so one
of you will have to stay at Joey's.
Since the fire was kind of my fault,
you should get to stay here.
불낸 건 나니까
네가 이 방을 써라
Hey, hey, now. This was no one's
fault. It was an accident.
얘, 그건 누구의 잘못이
아니라 단순한 사고였어
It was my fault.
You should get the nice room.
그 사고 내가 쳤으니까
네가 좋은 방 쓰라고
Okay!
그래
You're the first guest
at "Hotel Monica."
레이첼, 넌 모니카 호텔의
첫 손님이야
모니카 호텔?
Hotel Monica!
Just tell me how you like your eggs.
아침에 계란을 얼마나
익힐지 미리 말해 줘
내가 침대로 갖다 줄게
I thought I'd bring them
to you in bed.
-You've been through so much.
-I have.
- 그동안 고생 많았지?
- 정말 힘들었어
This right here is where
I keep the pizza.
여긴 피자를 두는 곳이야
And that's where the napkin is.
저긴 냅킨 보관소
-What's that smell?
-I know! I don't...
이게 무슨 냄새지?
그러게 말이야
Oh, please, it was such a big class.
You never even noticed me.
학생이 얼마나 많았는데
날 기억할 리가 없어요
What? Of course I did.
You sat next to "Sleepy Sleeperson."
정말이야, 네 자리는
'잠탱이' 바로 옆이었잖아
Who?
누구요?
Oh. I had trouble remembering names,
so I came up with nicknames.
학생들 이름을 다 못 외워서
별명으로 기억할 때가 많아
The guy on the other side of you
was "Smelly Von Brown Shirt."
네 반대쪽에 앉은 애는
'땟국물 갈색셔츠'였고
그랬군요
Oh, yeah.
-So did you have a nickname for me?
-No. No.
그럼 제 별명도 지었어요?
아냐, 없어
있었잖아요, 말해봐요
Yes, you did. What was it?
그게...
"Cutie McPretty."
'어여쁜 귀염둥이'
Oh, that's so sweet!
맘에 드네요
저기, 솔직히 얘기하면
오늘 정말 즐거웠어
Listen, I gotta tell you,
I'm having a great time.
You said it might be weird,
the whole student/teacher thing?
스승하고 제자 사이라
불편할 것 같다고 했잖아?
And to be frank,
I thought it would be too.
물론 내 생각도 그랬지만
지금은 전혀 이상하지 않아
But it's not.
I mean, it's not at all.
-Dr. Geller!
-Burt!
- 겔러 박사
- 버트
간밤엔 잘 잤니?
-Did you sleep well last night?
-I did.
그럼, 모니카가 머리맡에
박하를 놔뒀지 뭐겠어?
Monica was so sweet.
She left a little mint on my pillow.
Know what Joey left on my pillow?
- 조이는 뭘 뒀는지 아니?
- 뭔데?
Gum.
껌
-We determined the cause of the fire.
-I know. It was my candle, my candle!
화재원인이 밝혀졌습니다
알아요, 내 초 때문이겠죠
No, there was an appliance left on.
It looks like a curling iron.
아닙니다, 욕실에
전열기가 있더군요
머리 마는 도구 같던데
난 그런 거 안 써요
-I don't use a curling iron.
-Someone does.
다른 사람이 썼겠죠
Don't look at me, my hair's straight.
Straight, straight, straight.
뭐, 내 머린 스트레이트야
일사천리로 뻗었어
-It could've been a hair straightener.
-Oh.
머리 펴는 거 아닌가요?
This is where I keep the pizza.
여긴 피자를 두는 곳이야
저긴... 냅킨 어디 갔어?
And..
Hey, where'd the napkin go?
What is that?
이게 뭐지?
Is that old shrimp?
오래된 새우 아냐?
I think it is!
바로 그거다
I wouldn't want my best guest
to strain her eyes.
불 켜줄게, 손님의
눈을 보호해야지
Thanks, Monica.
고마워, 모니카
냄새 신경 안 쓰여?
-Does that smell bother you?
-From Joey's?
조이 집 냄새가
여기까진 안 올 텐데?
I can hardly smell it over here.
Well, you let me know if you can.
I can bake a pie to cover it.
혹시 냄새나면 말해
파이를 구워서 가려줄게
-I can smell it a little, bake a pie.
-Okay.
조금 난다, 파이 구워라
- 알았어
- 그래
Hello?
여보세요?
네, 잠깐만요
One minute, please.
It's the fire inspector.
받아, 소방검열관이래
Hello? Yeah, this is Phoebe.
여보세요?
네, 제가 피비인데요
Really?
정말요?
Yeah, so it turns out that it wasn't
the hair straightener...
네, 화재원인은 머리 펴는
기구가 아닌 것 같습니다
that started the fire.
No, no. It was the candles.
그럼요, 초 때문입니다
Yeah. It's very not good
leaving candles unattended.
아무도 없을 때
촛불을 켜두면 안 되죠
In fact, one of the first things
they teach you in fire school is...
사실 소방학교에서
처음 배우는 게 바로...
okay, well I have to go now.
그럼 이만 끊겠습니다
정말 즐거웠어
괜찮은 애더라고
We had such a great time.
She's incredible.
I thought the age difference might be
a problem, but it wasn't.
나이가 문제될 줄 알았는데
전혀 그렇지 않았어
Elizabeth is very mature for her age.
나이에 비해서
굉장히 성숙한 애야
A concept lost on some people.
개념 파악이 안 되는
녀석들도 있지
학생을 만나도 괜찮은 거야?
It's okay to date a student?
Well, not really. Technically,
it's not against the rules.
뭐 딱히 안 된다는 법이 있는 건
아니지만 좋게 보이진 않겠지
But it's frowned upon, especially by
the professor we saw last night:
특히 어젯밤에 부딪힌
'고결한 심판자' 교수한테는
"Judgy Von Holier-than-thou."
조심해, 잘못하다간
'제자 킬러' 교수되겠다
You don't want to get a reputation
as "Professor McNails-his-students."
-Yeah. What should I do?
-Well, it seems pretty clear.
어떡하면 좋겠냐?
간단한 문제잖아
What's more important?
What people think or how you feel?
뭐가 더 중요해?
남들의 평판, 네 느낌?
-You gotta follow your heart.
-Joey, that's so sweet.
가슴을 따라가
조이, 너 제법이다
-Hi.
-Hey! So how'd it go with Dana?
나 왔다
그래, 데이나는 만나봤어?
내 스케줄 비워둘까?
목요일쯤?
Any reason I should leave a block
of time open? Say, Thursday?
-I couldn't do it.
-You couldn't do it?
- 얘기 못했어
- 못했다고?
I need more time.
We're going to dinner.
진정해, 시간이 필요하겠어
오늘 저녁 먹기로 했다
뭐? 그 여자를 또 만나?
You're going out with her again?
-Going out with who?
-Dana Keystone, from college.
누굴 만나는데?
대학동창 데이나 키스톤
그래, 얘 말이야?
Oh, yeah. Wasn't she...?
No, that was Dana Kaplan.
그건 데이나 카플란이고
Oh.
조이, 넌 모르잖아
-Joey, you didn't even know her!
-Yeah, whatever.
아무렴 어때
Great story again.
굉장한 스토리네
엄청 탄탄하다
The yarns that you weave!
You know, actually, I should get going.
있잖아, 나 그만 가야겠어
안 돼, 가지 마
넌 거기 그냥 있어야 돼
Oh, no, no, stay!
Because you should stay.
Oh, I am really flattered.
기분은 정말 좋지만...
But I just...
I don't feel that way about you.
난 너한테 그런 감정 없어
Oh, no, no. That's not..
아냐, 그런 게 아니고
I'm sorry, Chandler.
You know, you're such a sweet guy...
미안해, 챈들러
넌 괜찮은 애야
and I don't want to hurt you.
상처 주고 싶지 않아
I wish I could do something
to make you feel better.
내가 어떡하면 위로가 되겠니
아니... 진심이야?
No.. Really?
Of course.
물론이지
가슴이 찢어지는 것 같다
Well, it just hurts so bad, I...
Oh, I'm sorry.
정말 미안해
-Maybe there is one thing you can do.
-What? Anything. Anything.
네가 해줄 수 있는 일이
한 가지 있긴 한데
뭔데? 뭐든 말해봐
Well, I mean, this is just
off the top of my head now.
이건 갑자기 떠오른 생각인데
But I have this friend..
This actor friend.
친구 놈 중에 배우가 하나 있거든
이 사실을 알면 날 죽이려 들 거야
He would kill me if he knew
that I was doing this.
But...
하지만...
would it be possible for him to
audition for your movie on Thursday?
그 녀석 네 영화 오디션에
나갈 수 있을까? 목요일쯤?
그럼
Absolutely.
But...
하지만...
you'd really feel better if your
friend could audition for my movie?
친구를 오디션에 내보낸다고
내가 준 상처가 치료되겠어?
The heart wants what it wants. Bye.
지금 내 맘은 그래, 또 보자
Hey! How's it going?
얘, 별일 없니?
Well, not much has changed
in the last five minutes.
뭐 5분전이랑 비슷해
Yes, it has. I made cookies!
아니지, 내가 쿠키를 구웠거든
I'm still full from your
homemade potato chips.
됐어, 아까 먹은 감자칩도
아직 안 내려갔어
But you should eat them now,
because they're hot from the oven.
그래도 먹어봐, 오븐에서
방금 꺼내 따끈따끈해
Okay.
- 알았어
- 여기선 안 되지
But not in here! Can't eat them
in bed, remember? No crumbies!
침대에선 곤란해
부스러기 떨어져
Oh. Okay, I'll be out in a second.
- 금방 나갈게
- 알았어
Okay.
지금 뭐한 거야?
-What are you doing?
-This doesn't lock, does it?
이 문 안 잠기는구나?
-Oh! Joey, I'm sorry.
-It's all right, don't worry about it.
조이, 미안하다
괜찮아, 별 걱정을 다 하네
이걸 봐
But look!
That's gonna leave a stain.
얼룩지게 생겼다
Rach, hey, it's fine.
You're at Joey's.
레이첼, 괜찮다니까
여긴 조이의 집이야
-Really?
-Yeah, look.
- 정말?
- 그럼, 볼래?
Yeah.
-I've never lived like this before.
-I know.
- 난 이렇게 살아본 적이 없어서
- 그렇겠지
일부러 버리진 마, 아깝게
Well, don't waste it.
I mean, it's still food.
What do you want to do now?
Want to get a drink?
이제 뭐하고 싶어?
술이나 한 잔 할까?
I can't.
안 돼요
-Oh, you have some studying to do?
-No, I have some turning 21 to do.
과제가 있나 보지?
아뇨, 아직 21살이 안 돼서
You know, I remember when I was
in college, we used to..
우리가 대학 다닐 땐 말이야...
-What are you doing?
-Nothing, I'm so comfortable with you.
뭐하세요?
아냐, 그냥 너하고
있으니까 참 편해서
Do you not want to be seen with me?
저랑 있는 거
들킬까봐 그래요?
말도 안 되는 소리
그 사람들 나갔니?
No, of course I do. Are they gone?
No, they're still here.
But I think I'm about to leave.
아뇨, 아직 계시지만
전 이만 가야겠어요
What? No, no, wait, wait..
뭐? 안 돼, 잠깐만
You're right, this is stupid.
Who cares what people think?
맞아, 바보 같은 짓이야
남들 평판이 무슨 상관이야
우린 서로를 좋아하는데
I mean, we like each other, right?
There's nothing wrong with that.
잘못된 거 없잖아?
Come on.
이리 와
Burt. Lydia. Mel.
버트? 리디아?
멜?
- 이쪽은 엘리자베스예요
- 안녕하세요
-This is Elizabeth.
-Hi.
Aren't you in my popular culture
class?
내 대중문화론 듣는
학생 아닌가?
That's right, Lydia.
Elizabeth is a student.
맞습니다
엘리자베스는 학생인데
저랑 사귀고 있죠
And we're dating.
And you may frown upon that but...
손가락질하셔도 좋지만
we're not gonna hide it anymore.
더 이상 숨기지 않겠어요
You are so fired.
자넨 해고야
-What?
-They'll fire you.
네?
해고라니까, 학생과
사귀는 건 교칙위반이야
You can't date her.
It's against the rules.
Really? It's not just frowned upon?
그냥 손가락질 정도가 아니고?
그렇지
I love it at Joey's!
조이 집 너무 좋다
여기 또 있어
-Nice!
-Thanks.
- 좋다
- 고마워
So you busy Thursday?
너 목요일에 바쁘냐?
그래, 웃긴다
Oh, very funny. Remember?
My audition was supposed to be Thursday.
넌 잊었는지 모르지만
목요일엔 오디션이 있어
You got me the audition?
Let's hug it up!
내 오디션 따왔구나
안아줄게
Okay, okay! What are you
gonna do to me if you get the part?
그래, 됐어
잘되면 나한테 뭐해줄래?
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
-Hey.
-Hi.
- 나 왔다
- 그래
Yeah, okay, I need to talk to you.
- 저기, 너한테 할말이 있어
- 뭔데?
I know they said the hair straightener
started the fire.
머리 펴는 기구 때문에 불이
났다고 했지만 내 잘못도 있어
But I think I'm partly at fault.
You see, I didn't tell you, but...
너한테는 말 안 했지만
내가 최근에 티슈를
다시 채워놨거든
I had recently refilled
the tissues.
And so, let's face it,
that's just kindling.
그 때문에 불이 붙은 거야
So I think it's fair that
I stay at Joey's.
그니까 내가 조이 집에
있는 게 낫겠어
No, no, no, this was my fault.
아냐, 그건 내 잘못이야
난 여기 있어도 괜찮아
-Besides, I'm fine here.
-Okay.
알았어
-Chandler, Monica's looking for you.
-Really?
- 챈들러, 모니카가 찾더라
- 그래?
-She said something about crumbies.
-No, no, no! I was so careful.
부스러기가 어쩌고 하던데
저런, 조심한다고 했는데
You have to switch with me.
Monica is driving me crazy.
됐다, 나랑 집 바꾸자
모니카 때문에 미치겠어
That's right. All the ladies
want to stay at Joey's.
아무렴, 여자들은 다
조이랑 살려고 하지
No, I don't want to switch.
안 돼, 난 정말 바꾸기 싫어
여기서 물티슈 던지고 놀래
Please! I can throw
wet paper towels here!
모니카 집에선 싱크대에 대고
과자도 먹을 수 있어
No, but at Monica's,
you can eat cookies over the sink.
I know. I'm sorry.
알아
미안하다
All right, fine.
그래, 됐어
This looks like so much fun.
God, what a mess.
이거 재미있겠다
난장판이네
Wow, it actually is in the handbook.
정말 요람에 나와 있어
I can't date you or have
a hot plate in my office.
학생과 교제할 수도 없고
사무실에 난로를 둬서도 안 돼
I can't believe we have
to stop seeing each other.
우리가 이렇게
헤어져야 되다니
For what it's worth, I did appreciate
you standing up for me.
그래도 괜찮아요
절 위해 나서주셨잖아요
That felt really nice.
정말 기분 좋았어요
Kind of made me like you even more.
교수님이 더 좋아진 것 같아요
I know, I know. I really like
you too. But we can't date.
알아, 나도 네가 좋지만
우리 이제 만나면 안 돼
It's against the rules.
It's forbidden.
교칙으로 금지한다니
어쩔 수 있나
-Wow.
-What?
왜?
금지라는 말을 들으니까
더 흥분되네요
Just hearing you describe it
as "forbidden"...
it's really hot.
Really?
정말?
Yeah.
네
Well, I don't care how hot it is,
it's wrong.
아무리 흥분이 돼도
이건 옳지 않아
-Stop it.
-No, no. It's wrong.
그만해요
안 돼, 이건 잘못된 일이야
용서받지 못할 짓이라고
It's naughty.
It's...
이건...
taboo.
터부야
Shut the book.
책 덮어요
Hey. Let's also get a hot plate.
난로도 들여놓자고
Hey.
- 나다
- 그래
Hey.
어때?
-So?
-So...?
뭐가?
It's Thursday!
How was the audition?
목요일이잖아
오디션 말이야
It's.. Monday, one day. Tuesday,
two day. Wednesday, what day..
목요일...
하나는 월요일, 둘은 화요일
셋은 수요일, 수요일 다음은...
Oh!